©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
As I was going up the stair
I met a man who wasn 't there
He wasn 't there again today
I wish I wish he 'd go away
Where did you learn that ?
Where did you learn that poem ?
I made it up .
When I was a kid , I made it up .
What else do you remember from back then ?
Don 't beat around the bush , doc .
Don 't beat around the bush .
Don 't beat around the bush , doc !
Tell me what you remember about your mother .
I remember my mom .
I remember my mom was a whore .
How long would she keep you there ?
As long as she was busy .
Do you understand why you 're talking with me now ?
You 're supposed to be good with
headaches .
I need something more than aspirin .
Know what I mean ?
Do you remember the murders ?
I remember
that Columbia is the capital of South Carolina .
I remember that- -
Are you the person who murdered six residents
of the Lakeworth Apartments on May 10 , 1998 ?
That 's my birthday .
Who am I speaking to right now ?
What should I call you ?
Call me whatever you want .
Gary ?
Gary , you awake ?
Yes , Greg , as a matter of fact , I am awake .
I 'm sorry to bother you at home
but there 's gonna be a midnight hearing in the Rivers case .
The defense found a notebook misfiled in evidence , a diary .
They argued to the state Supremes that it was suppressed .
What are you talking about ?
There 's no media .
This all happened under the radar .
The prisoner transport left an hour ago from Ely .
Left Ely ? What do you mean ?
What transport ?
The diary gave them an opening to argue insanity again .
They need Rivers present , so they drugged him , put him on a transport .
They 're taking this scumbag to a hearing
the night before his execution .
How the fuck did you let that happen ?
Would anyone like to play another round ?
Let 's get another puzzle , Vanna . What do we have ?
- " Around the House " is the category . - Buy a vowel .
- Buy a vowel . - Pick up that trip .
Buy a vowel , you idiot .
I 'd like to buy a vowel . An E.
One E.
- All right , 350 left . - N .
- Buy a vowel . - Buy another vowel .
- Yes ! - An I.
- I 'd like to solve . - Sure .
" Kibbles ' n Bits . "
She won 't stop bleeding .
Jesus . What happened ?
An accident . We had an accident .
Rain and lightning is moving into Elko .
Doppler Radar has picked up a severe thunderstorm with lightning
on its way from Pershing and Lander counties .
We could get damaging winds ... .
Four times 10 equals- -
Four times 10- -
Timothy , could you not do that now ?
We 're trying to hear about the storm .
- Sure you don 't want me to drive ? - No .
I 'll get us to Anderson , then you can take over after we eat .
Turn into spin .
Apply brakes with short , firm pumps .
Check mirror and gauge indicator and roll
to a slow , smooth stop .
You okay , honey ? Timothy ?
Seat belts , seat belts , seat belts .
- It 's a shoe . - What ?
It 's a shoe !
For he 's a jolly good fellow
Which nobody can deny
Shit !
Why didn 't we get a better spare ?
Do you know what radials cost , Alice ?
Honey , don 't get defensive .
Well , if the point is to put him , Timothy , into the right school ...
- ... it 's absurd to focus ... - George ? George ?
... on replacement tires .
What can I do to help ?
Nothing . I 'm fine , but
thank you .
Oh , my God !
Oh , my God ! Alice ?
What have you done ?
Hi , Harry . Where do I begin ?
I have walked off the set , okay ?
I know they 'll say that I am in breach
but they clearly did not read my deal .
They had me at a Ramada- -
Oh , Jesus .
I think I have a spare battery in my bag .
Excuse me ?
I have a spare battery in my bag up front , next to you .
Any idea which one , Miss Suzanne ?
The Louis Vuitton duffel , right on top .
I don 't see anything- -
Just use your fucking eyes !
It 's in the side pocket ! Just look !
Jesus !
What have you done ?
No , fool ! If you help him , you assume responsibility .
It is my responsibility .
Let go of me .
Alice ? Alice ?
What have you done ?
Let me take a look .
The driver of every motor vehicle involved in any manner of accident
originating from the operation of a vehicle shall , within 10 days ... .
You got a towel or something in the car ?
Okay . Come help me look .
- -within 10 days of the accident
if you are operating a vehicle and it should , at any time , involve- -
Stay here . Keep her dry .
It 's okay . It 's okay , honey .
- Open the door ! We need the phone . - No !
Sweetheart , it 's okay .
Honey , it 's okay .
Give me the goddamn phone !
The phone is dead , all right ?
You 're gonna be fine .
You 're gonna be okay .
No !
She won 't stop bleeding .
Jesus . What happened ?
There was an accident .
May I please use your phone ?
- Please use your phone ? - Yeah , sure .
Shit . I 'm not getting a line .
It happens in the rain .
The phone doesn 't work .
St. Jude 's has 24-hour emergency , 30 miles east .
Okay .
You sit here , okay ?
Keep pressure on the wound .
I 'll be back with an ambulance .
What are you doing ?
Sorry . It 's a step down from the Ramada , but it 'll have to do .
I am not staying here .
Are you out of your mind ?
This is my car .
You work for me .
Get those bags back in this car now !
I understand the bleeding person has a medical condition , but so do I.
My lung walls have depleted cilia .
If I stay here , I could asphyxiate !
No , please , please , please , please , please , please .
Please !
Hey !
Stop . Please , please .
Hi . I 'm sorry , my car is stuck .
Can I get a ride ?
Okay .
You know you 're going east .
Hospital 's this way .
It 's flooded .
I mean , it 's a dead end .
Yeah , well , if you don 't mind , I gotta try .
Okay , that will be $ 30 cash , please .
Didn 't you use to be that actress ?
Yes .
- Wow . - Now , is that a nice room ?
Because though I am leaving soon , I still would prefer a nice room .
Your nicest
if that is possible .
Eight 's very cozy .
I tried to tell you .
Hey ! Hey , stop !
There 's no way through .
There 's no way through !
No way through !
- Lou , wake up . - What ?
Cell phone .
- What ? - Do you have a cell phone ?
Who wants to know ?
There 's been an accident , a bad one .
A lady 's hurt .
We need a cell phone right now .
Dude , slow down .
First , we don 't know who you are .
Second , we don 't see an accident- -
Listen to me , dude , I 'm having a really fucked-up , wet , bad fucking day .
So if you have a cell phone , give it to me now !
Dude , we don 't have a cell phone , so could you just let go of me now ? !
I need you to give me a lift in the other direction .
It 's flooded that way too .
It 's worse than this .
Ginny , pop the trunk . Let them in .
Let them in .
Hey . How you doing ?
Phone still dead ?
Yeah . Where 's your Lincoln ?
Stuck in a run-off two miles down the road .
The other way 's fucked too .
The kids gave us a lift .
The girl was stranded .
Is there another way out ?
Is she a hooker ?
Hey ! Is there a back road ?
Where do you think the water 's going ?
You wouldn 't get 500 feet .
How 's the woman ?
I don 't know .
They 're in number 4 .
I 'm sorry .
We don 't rent rooms by the hour .
Funny . You still serving food ?
Vending machines are around the corner . Go ahead .
Rooms are 30 bucks in advance with picture ID .
You need one room or two ?
Excuse me . I was talking to you .
I 'd appreciate it if you looked at me .
Well , I don 't like looking at trash .
We 're a little stuck here , George .
I don 't think we can get out tonight .
She just keeps shaking .
She 's in shock .
- Let me take a look . - What ?
Let me take a look .
Did your wife pack a sewing kit ?
No .
Ginny , wait up .
Six .
At least we got a good number .
- Did you feel that ? - Feel what ?
Cold .
Are you the manager ?
Yeah .
I 'm Officer Rhodes , Corrections .
I 'm transporting a prisoner here .
The law gives you the right to refuse us service
but the roads are flooded .
I could use a room .
It 's an emergency .
You got a radio in that car ?
- Who 's this ? - Limo driver , had an accident .
I got a lady pretty banged up .
I could use an ambulance .
Four-four-two requesting medical .
Nothing . It 's been like this for the past hour .
She 's losing a lot of blood .
Got a first aid kit ?
Band-Aids , that 's it .
How about a needle and thread ?
Maybe in the diner .
I 'll get it . Locked up .
Stay dry .
I 'll be back with your key .
I 'll put you in 10 .
Okay , thanks .
What do you got back there ?
Prison transfer .
Maybe when you get him situated , come to 4 and look at the lady .
- I could use a second opinion . - Yeah , sure .
Looks like you 're fucked .
Shut up !
I wish I had beige .
This is fine .
Would have been better .
I gotta get the officer situated .
Let me know if you need something .
I 'll be right back .
Where did you learn to do that ?
Pretty much where you 're standing .
Hey , is the ... ?
The little boy , is he all right ?
He hasn 't said a word since the accident .
No , no , no . He doesn 't talk much ever since the ... .
I 'm his stepfather .
His father ... .
Two years ago , he left .
Little temper problem .
Watch your step .
The furniture 's for shit .
If you 're fixing to cuff him to something , the toilet 's bolted down .
Thank you so much for your assistance .
It 's a good idea . Come on .
I got stripes
Stripes around my shoulders And these chains
These chains They 're about to- -
Let 's go look at that lady .
- You get anyone ? - What ?
- Did you get through ? - No , not yet .
Good stitch job .
Pulse is shallow , but steady .
Keep her comfortable .
We should take turns on the radio , if that 's all right .
No , it 's not . I can manage .
You gonna arrest me , officer ?
What ?
How 'd you do that ?
How 'd you know I was a cop ?
No shit .
Cheetos for dinner , huh ?
That don 't seem right .
You got a better idea ?
I worked mess in the service .
Maybe the diner 's open . I could- -
You got change for a dollar ?
I don 't know . Let me see .
Here you go .
You got a name ?
- Paris . - Paris , huh ?
I 'll get it .
Never been .
Well , you ain 't going tonight .
Please .
Please be strong .
You see , Timothy and I
we need you .
We need you so much .
Lou ?
You need to tell them , Harry , that I can 't work , I can 't perform
I can 't shine living in an environment like that .
No , it is not about the money .
It 's about the working conditions .
One bar .
No bar .
Two bars .
Come on . Come on .
Here we go .
There you go . Come on .
Goddamn desert wasteland !
Oh , shit !
I just had it .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
Holy fuck .
Jesus , Mother of God .
Who is this ?
The woman I was driving .
What the hell are you doing ?
There 's something in there .
- Use this , man . - Thanks .
- Are you a cop ? - I was .
- She was in Room 10 ? - I am .
Where 's your guy ?
Cuffed to a toilet .
Son of a bitch .
That was a fucking drive .
- Gentlemen . - Your Honor .
Ready , Sharon ? Alrighty .
In the matter of Rivers v. Nevada , for the purposes of- -
Judge Taylor , sir , with due respect , we should wait till my client arrives .
He has a right to be present .
He has precious few rights .
He 's 24 hours from execution .
But to demonstrate his mental state , which is the purpose- -
His mental state ?
Do you know what time it is ?
You think I got time for bullshit ?
That the justices called me in the middle of the night to review a case
I already sat on , that I already decided , may make you happy .
But it pisses me off .
When your boy gets here , do what you want , but in the name of decency
state your goddamn case !
Yes , sir .
Somebody get me a cup of coffee , black .
All right , everybody ! Listen up !
There was an incident tonight .
That 's police talk for , " Someone 's head got lopped off . "
Larry !
- Caroline Suzanne was murdered . - What ?
Who 's Caroline Suzanne ?
The actress I was driving .
And where exactly did that happen ?
We don 't know , because we can 't find the body .
Not all of it anyway .
What do you mean , you can 't find it ?
Stay calm . Everything will be all right .
Officer Rhodes is outside .
He was transporting a convict .
- Who escaped . - What are you- - ?
- Hold on . - Running free !
Will you shut the fuck up so he can talk ?
This is my place , ho !
I 'll say what I please !
It 's safe here .
It is not safe here !
There 's a cop here .
Yeah , two cops .
Wait . You 're a cop ?
I was . Shut up , Larry !
It 's not safe here !
I 'm not staying- -
It 's all right . It 's okay .
Nothing .
- Is she okay ? - Ginny .
Ginny , will you ... ?
Stop it . Don 't do this right now .
What are you doing ?
Put your arm around your girlfriend .
Actually , she 's my wife .
Everybody just stay here .
Stay in this room .
Wait ! I 'm not staying here if he is .
- Yes , you are . - No , I 'm not .
- I 'm not . - All right . Larry ?
- Come with us . - Why ?
You know the place .
Here 's what I know .
I 'm not a cop .
I don 't take orders from a professional slut !
- Fuck you ! - Listen . Just stay here , please .
Keep everybody calm .
He 's not gonna get too far .
Not in this !
Rhodes !
What are we chasing here ?
Multiple homicide .
I 'll go around this way .
Meet you in back .
Is that where you live full-time ? Las Vegas ?
- Used to . - What 's that supposed to mean ?
It means I don 't live there anymore .
Maine !
We 'll go see if we can use this one .
We 'll go in here .
Since that wasn 't a successful attempt , we 'll go in here .
I 'll be right out here . It 's okay .
I 'm gonna stand guard .
Not a worry .
I 'll be right here .
I 'm not going anywhere .
See , his mother usually does this .
Hey , Ginny .
So how long you two been married ?
About nine hours .
It was a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing .
Viva Las Vegas , huh , Gin ?
We need to leave !
I was just talking to her .
Something 's happening !
I need to get out of here !
Ginny ! Ginny !
You don 't own me , Lou !
I own what 's inside you !
Half , at least .
You don 't own any part of me or my baby !
Then why did I marry you ?
- Don 't slam the goddamn door on me ! - Hey ! Hey !
You guys , just calm down !
We are not leaving .
There is no place else to go .
There 's a flood outside , Ginny .
Stop it ! Stop it !
I 'm not pregnant !
What did you just say ?
I lied .
I 'm not pregnant .
What are you talking about ?
I saw the test .
Why would you do that to me ?
Because Alison saw you at The Hawk with that fucking girl !
- Ginny , what are we , like 15 ? - Go away !
Goddamn !
- Open this goddamn door , Ginny ! - No !
I haven 't been to The Hawk in over a fucking year .
Alison is a stupid bitch-whore , who likes fucking with your head .
Open the damn door , Ginny .
Open the fucking door !
Not until you calm down !
I 'm calm ! I am very fucking calm !
What are you doing ?
Lou ?
Ginny , open this damn door !
Open the door !
- Open the door ! - Stop it , stop it !
Ginny , damn it , open the door !
Ginny , Ginny , Ginny !
Lou , please stop !
Lou ?
Oh , my God !
Help me !
Somebody help me !
Is he in there ?
Ginny , are you okay ?
What happened ? What happened ?
- Oh , shit . - Jesus Christ .
Lou ? Lou ?
What 's going on ?
What the hell ?
Oh , shit !
Come here !
They caught him .
Why are we keeping him in here ?
Where would you prefer , Larry ?
I don 't know .
I told you to stay in 3 , didn 't I ?
Did I tell you that ?
They got in a fight !
I tried to get them to go back inside !
Should we try the radio again ?
Larry , just stay here and watch him .
Go back and look after Ginny .
Where are you going ?
Just do it , please .
Ed ?
I don 't know if I 'm comfortable with guard duty , per se .
He 's unconscious , Larry .
He 's tied to a post .
Timothy .
Alice ? Oh , my God . Alice ?
I don 't remember anything .
We had an accident .
George ? Can you keep an eye on Ginny for a minute ?
She 's awake now .
I have to get some aspirin to help her .
Darling , I gotta go get something out of my room .
- Shit ! - What 's wrong , buddy ?
What do you got in the fridge ?
You shut up .
What 's in there ?
- What do you got in there ? - Shut up .
What is it , huh ?
- Shut up . - You can tell me .
I 'm good at keeping secrets .
I got a whopper myself .
What are you doing ?
Motherfucker !
What are you doing out here ?
Getting shit that 's mine .
What are you doing ?
What , I don 't get to ask a question ?
I 'm taking photos .
There 's been two murders .
Before all the evidence- -
That 's not an answer .
You 're a limo driver .
What are you doing ?
Looking to win some " beyond the call of duty , " limo-driver merit badge ?
You 're not on the job anymore .
You don 't need to be a hero .
There 's a real , live , active-duty cop outside- -
The one who 's managed to lose a convicted killer ?
You 're a complicated cat , Edward .
No . Not really .
I think so .
What month were you born ?
- May . - Taurus .
Same as me .
Where were you a cop ?
Los Angeles .
Were you fired or did you quit ?
I took medical leave .
It was making me sick .
I burned out , I guess .
Wasn 't up for it .
One day I got a call
for a jumper .
A young Mexican girl .
Pregnant , infected with AIDS , totally strung-out .
She was truly one of the doomed .
I asked her to come in off the ledge and into my arms .
She asked me why she should bother living .
What did you say ?
I was trained to tell her lots of things .
Her dreams , all the people who 'd miss her .
But for a second , I hesitated .
And she saw it .
Within that second , I couldn 't think of one optimistic thing to say to her .
So she spread her arms and jumped .
I started getting headaches
and eventually started blacking out .
So I filed for medical .
What ?
What is it ?
Rhodes !
It 's worse . Nothing but static !
Where 's that key from the actress ?
This was on the kid .
- What is it , some kind of countdown ? - Larry !
What the fuck is he doing ?
Larry , come over here !
Come over here , man .
What are you doing ?
Come over here .
I just went to get something .
We told you to watch the guy .
What are you doing in your office ?
I just went to get something .
How many sets of keys are there to this place ?
Look at me . How many ?
Two and a master set .
Oh , my fucking God !
Larry , you mother- - ! You son of a- - !
Get the fuck in here ! Get in here !
Why did you kill him ?
Why did you kill my con ?
Holy shit ! Who did that ?
Jesus Christ , I didn 't do that !
Bullshit ! You 're lying !
It 's your bat sticking out of his throat !
I know , but I didn 't do it !
Check the doors !
- I didn 't do it ! - Look at him !
Why 'd you kill him ?
Why were you outside ?
Why 'd you leave him ?
I was scared .
What were you scared of ?
You wouldn 't understand .
Try me .
- Why 'd you kill my con ? - I didn 't !
I don 't know how- - I went
to my office , that 's all !
Why 'd you leave him ?
This your key ? Number 8 ?
Ten , nine , eight , huh ?
This is your key !
You can 't say that !
Those aren 't my keys !
That 's like leading the witness or something . Look .
These are my keys , okay ?
These are my keys . You see ?
You got a Gucci wallet ?
It 's the actress 's .
Yes , I took her wallet .
Afterwards . After she died !
Afterwards , all right ?
I didn 't kill her .
And I didn 't kill him .
Let her go , Larry .
Get back ! You won 't pin this on me .
- Timothy ? - Get him out of here !
Put it down .
I didn 't hurt anybody . No one !
But I don 't like cheap fucking whores !
If you take one more step- -
Fuck !
Get it off !
Shit !
Come on , you little bitch .
Please fucking start .
- Goddamn it ! - Hey !
Larry , stop !
What is going on ?
- Larry ! - Get out of my way , I didn 't do shit !
Timothy ! Timothy !
An insanity plea was refused by the court
despite the fact that my client is a certifiable Axis IV dissociative .
To this day , he remains unaware of the crimes for which he was convicted .
In 1986 , the Supreme Court ruled decisively that states cannot execute
a person who does not understand why he 's being put to death .
He signed a confession .
- He didn 't just sign it , he dictated it . - Thirdly
Malcolm 's diaries found misfiled in state evidence .
Your Honor , this notebook contains entries made just before the murders .
Important to note are the spectacular changes in handwriting style
tone , point of view .
What you are looking at are the private thoughts of several different people .
With permission , Dr. Mallick will elaborate .
Thank you .
Your Honor , there is no universally efficacious treatment
for Dissociative Identity Disorder .
In theory , one attempts to move the patient towards integration .
- A folding of their fractured psyche . - Your Honor ?
He 's here .
No ! What you saw was an accident !
He ran out in front of me !
I 'm not a murderer !
There 's a dead body in your freezer , Larry .
I didn 't kill him .
I found him like that . Stop it !
Listen ! Listen ! I was in Vegas last month and I lost everything , okay ?
Everything !
I drove west .
I didn 't know where to go , but I was running on empty
so I pulled in here at this place .
And there was no one at the station , so I came over to the office
and I walked in .
And there , sitting at that desk right there , was the manager
facedown in a Banquet Potpie . Dead !
Heart attack or something .
Banquet Potpie !
He 'd been sitting there for God knows how long .
All of a sudden , this auto-parts salesman pulls up , looking for a room .
I didn 't have a fucking dime
so I took his 30 and gave him one .
I just took the key from the wall and gave him a room .
Maybe that was wrong , but I was broke , and that 's what I did .
Then I came back in here
and I moved Larry 's body- -
His name was Larry too .
I put him in the freezer .
I wasn 't trying to hide him .
It was hot out .
I thought it was the best place for him till his family or someone came along .
Only no one did
except more guests .
So I checked them in too .
And they all seemed happy
so I just stayed .
Cry me a river .
This is a total crock of shit !
- No , it 's not ! - Admit it , you killed him !
Just like you killed my con .
Just like you killed her husband .
Just like you killed his actress .
Just admit it .
- Say it , " I killed them . " - Stop it !
He can 't take any more !
Everything is okay now .
Everything is fine .
We got the guy . It 's fine .
- I don 't know what we got . - What ?
We thought we got the guy two hours ago , then- -
You believe this shit ?
It 's him ! It 's this guy !
He had a knife to your neck , remember ?
His story 's so unbelievable , I think it just might be true .
She 's got a point .
You guys are crazy .
Maybe it 's the burial ground .
What ?
Read the brochure in there .
It 's all around us .
A hundred years ago , the government moved these Indians here .
They all died because there was no water .
Now they 're coming back to life like sea monkeys , huh ?
Come on . Give me a break , sweetheart .
Just take it easy , Rhodes .
You know , you take it easy !
You 've tried to run this show all night .
Giving orders , pointing fingers !
You blamed my con for everything , and he ends up dead .
I 'm telling you , it 's him !
We all saw him run down George .
Your actress 's wallet is right there .
She 's dead , there 's the wallet .
What more do you want ?
Stop it ! Please shut up !
All right . You want a plan ?
Here 's the plan , okay ?
No one 's gonna move .
We 'll stay here , like this , in this room until dawn .
No one leaves , no one moves .
And if he tries anything , I 'm gonna shoot him !
And if something out there comes in here , I 'll shoot it !
And if anyone of us tries anything , I 'll shoot them !
- We get it . - Good !
Timmy ? Timmy ?
You need to stay in here with us .
It 's all right .
Remember that movie where the 10 strangers went to an island
and then they all died one by one
and then it turned out they weren 't strangers , they all had a connection ?
They all messed with the wrong guy , and he was getting revenge .
Shut up !
I 'm just saying maybe there 's a connection between all of us .
Like what ?
- We 're all in Nevada . - Shut up !
Where were you going with your con when you pulled in here ?
Carson City . Okay ?
I was going home to Florida .
Where were you going ?
I was taking the actress to L.A.
I was born in Florida .
Since you been in that chair , no one 's died , so shut up !
No one 's died since we 've all been here !
Hey , sweetie , sit down .
Where in Florida , Larry ?
Where in Florida ?
Friends now , huh ? Great .
- Polk County . - That 's where I was born .
- Which town ? - Mulberry .
- Frostproof . - No wonder you left .
There 's a town called Frostproof ?
They grow oranges .
The name doubles as a slogan .
I danced hallelujah the day I left Polk .
Why would you wanna go back ?
I found a grove for sale on the Internet .
Nine acres , 1200 trees .
Limes and oranges .
According to the realtor , the soil needs a few tills , phosphorous
lanes need reading , but it 's real good land .
What ?
It sounds nice .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
Ed ?
She 's dead .
Get him out of here .
Come on . Come on , sweetie .
Look at this .
- Where 'd you get that ? - Right here .
This doesn 't make any sense .
She died from an accident .
George was an accident , if you believe Larry .
Where is seven ?
Back it up !
See , I told you it wasn 't me !
That 's not possible .
I was standing right there .
I saw what happened .
We all saw what happened .
He ran out . Nobody could have known he was gonna do that .
No one human .
We 're back to that again ?
It 's the spirits , huh ?
Maybe it 's the ghost of the guy that Larry put in the freezer .
Somebody untie me . Goddamn it !
You know it wasn 't me . Come on .
- Listen . - We gotta get out- -
Take her car and get out .
You , her and the kid .
There 's nowhere to go .
- How much gas do you have ? - Half a tank .
You can drive till dawn on that .
Look at me .
When you get to where it 's flooded , go the other way .
I don 't know if I can .
Get the kid and go . Right now . Come on .
Timmy .
Timmy , come on . Let 's go . Get up .
What 's going on ?
- They can 't leave ! - This way .
We 'll see you when the storm breaks .
Hey ! Hey ! They can 't leave !
Where are they going ? Get back here !
Go , go , go ! They 're leaving .
- They 're not leaving . - Go !
You can 't let suspects leave after four people have been killed !
You really think they 're suspects ?
They 're not leaving !
Shit .
Ginny !
Extinguishers . Larry , you got a fire extinguisher ?
- Fire extinguisher ! Where ? - Back there !
Nobody in there .
Maybe it got so hot , they got cremated .
There 'd be something left .
You did this .
You did this !
You told them to get into the car !
Are you happy ?
Where is he ?
Nothing .
I give up !
I give up ! What the hell do you want ?
What do you want , you sick bastard ?
What the fuck do you want from us ?
I am turning 30 next week and I just want to go home
and grow oranges !
It 's your birthday next week ?
It 's my birthday next week . The 10th .
Me too .
Yeah .
George York , May 10 .
Alice York , May 10 .
Caroline Suzanne , May 10 .
Ginny and Lou Isiana , May 10 .
Me , Larry Washington , May fucking 10 .
What are the odds ?
Must be 10 trillion-to-one .
What is it ?
Where 's the fuse box , Larry ?
Other side of the building .
Ginny and Lou Isiana .
Virginia and Louisiana .
Caroline , Carolina .
Paris Nevada .
George York .
Larry Washington .
Rhodes , Rhode Island .
Ed Dakota .
When I was going up the stairs I met a man who wasn 't there
He wasn 't there again today
I wish I wish he 'd go away
Who is this ?
Who am I speaking to right now ?
Where did you learn that poem ?
Who am I speaking to ? Look at me .
Who am I speaking to right now ?
Doc ?
- Edward ? - What 's happening ?
Please be quiet .
He can hear what we 're saying ?
Of course I can hear what you 're fucking saying .
Edward , you missed your last appointment .
Where have you been ?
Did I black out again ?
Try and think back .
Where have you been ?
All right . I was driving this actress
and we got stuck at the motel .
There was a storm .
We couldn 't get out because of the storm .
What happened at the motel ?
People started dying .
And then their bodies- -
It didn 't make any sense .
They disappeared .
Edward , I 'd like to show something to you , if I may .
Do you recognize this man ?
No .
That man , Edward , is Malcolm Rivers .
He 's had a very troubled life .
He was arrested four years ago
and convicted of the murder of six people in a violent rampage .
- He did this . - Detective , please .
Edward , listen to me .
When faced with an intense trauma , a child 's mind may fracture
creating disassociated identities .
That 's exactly what happened to Malcolm Rivers .
He developed a condition that is commonly known
as Multiple Personality Syndrome .
Why are you telling me this ?
Because you , Edward
are one of his personalities .
What ?
Jesus Christ ! What the fuck did you do to my face ?
- Keep calm . - Where is my face ?
That is your face .
Why am I tied up ?
- Keep calm . - Where is- - ?
- Please . - Jesus Christ !
- Where is my face ? - Stay calm .
No ! I 'm not gonna stay calm !
Why am I tied up like this ?
Who are all these people ?
What happened at the motel ?
Where is everybody ?
They don 't exist , Edward .
You were all created by Malcolm as a child .
You 're a liar !
Consider what you know .
- Everyone named after a state . - No .
Everyone sharing the same birthday . Your blackouts .
No ! I was a cop !
I was a cop in the Rampart Division of L.A.P.D. for six years .
Edward , please .
I live in Hollywood , in a studio apartment .
You don 't live there .
I do live there !
You don 't live anywhere .
I know this is difficult to accept , but the face you saw in that mirror
is the face I 've always seen when I talk to Edward or Paris or Larry
or anyone else you 've met tonight .
Malcolm is in the midst of a medical treatment .
One which forces all his identities to confront one another for the first time .
I knew there would be violence
and with it , the number of the identities would be reduced .
Reduced ?
One of the personalities you 've met tonight , Edward ...
He took control of Malcolm 's body , as you have now
and released an unspeakable rage .
And in 19 hours
Malcolm Rivers will be put to death because of those actions
unless I can convince that man
that the killer is gone .
I need you to stay with me . Edward ?
I need your help .
I need your help to finish this .
Edward , listen to me .
Edward , stay with me .
Listen to me .
I need you to understand .
The killer cannot survive .
Edward !
Got it ?
I can 't see a thing .
Is there a flashlight ?
Hang on . Hang on .
You got a flashlight ?
Yeah , yeah , it 's dead . Goddamn it .
Shut up !
Hey . What am I supposed to wear , man ?
You 're in it .
Larry .
Larry , come here .
Ed !
Larry ?
Larry ? Larry ?
Where are the keys to the truck ?
That was good , Larry .
We gotta get out of here .
Ed has the keys to the truck .
I got a spare right here .
Where is he ?
I don 't know . Here .
What are you doing ?
We need a gun .
Holy shit !
Give me the keys to the truck .
Ed !
We gotta get out of here !
- Paris-- - He 's coming . He 's- -
- Stay here . - What 's wrong with you ?
Paris , listen to me .
Stay here .
It 's gonna be okay .
Throw me the keys to the truck , Ed .
Throw me the keys to the truck .
Stay there . Stay there !
Ed ! Ed ! Ed !
Ed , let me see .
We gotta get you to a hospital .
We 're gonna get you to a hospital , okay ?
Stay with me because I 'm gonna get you to the truck .
Put your arm around my neck .
You gotta hold on , okay ?
You with me , Ed ?
Stay with me .
Okay . One , two , three .
You gotta help me get you up .
Ed , you gotta push a little bit .
Ed , why won 't you let me help you ?
Where did you go before ?
What did you see ?
Tell me what you saw .
I saw you .
I saw you in an orange grove .
Why won 't you let me help you ?
Where did you go ?
What did you see ?
I saw you
in an orange grove .
The question , Your Honor , is whether to convict the body or the mind .
His body committed these murders , that is true .
The person who remains inside did not .
Judge Taylor , that may not be true- -
We witnessed the destruction of 10 identities tonight .
Nine were innocent and one was guilty .
They 're not real !
The violence that existed in him has been executed .
Your Honor , Malcolm belongs in a state hospital .
In the matter of Rivers v. Nevada , it is the recommendation of this court
that Mr. Rivers ' execution be stayed .
I am transferring Mr. Rivers to state psychiatric services
under the care of Dr. Mallick .
Cracked heels and washed-out horns Blow into my face with scorn
But it 's not that way I wasn 't born to lose you
I want you
I want you so bad
Timmy .
No , please don 't .
No , Timmy , please .
What is it , Malcolm ?
Malcolm ?
Whores don 't get a second chance .
When I was going up the stairs
I met a man who wasn 't there
He wasn 't there again today
I wish I wish he 'd go away
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ